visionwidget.com 2017-03-23

# Privacy Policy

Category: [Marked](https://visionwidget.com/uncategorised/) Published: Saturday, 02 August 2014 08:12 

## Privacy Policy for visionwidget.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at **visionwidget$gmail.com (change $ to @).**

At **visionwidget.com** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by **visionwidget.com** and how it is used.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, **visionwidget.com** makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

**visionwidget.com** does't use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

### BuySellAds

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on **visionwidget.com** send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. visionwidget.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

Last Updated: Saturday, 02 August 2014 08:12
